Guide to the ILGWU. Sol Chaikin papers,
ILGWU. Sol Chaikin papers,
- Series VIII. Correspondence, 1953-1991
  - Imports. Rollback Campaign, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    Includes samples of form letters sent out by ILGWU urging support of legislation to roll-back apparel imports; resolution; and fact sheet.
  - Independent Unions, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Industrial Policy [folder 1 of 2], 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    Includes copies of legislative bills, plans for Conference on Industrial Policy (Chaikin, Keynote Speaker); 19 p. testimony of Chaikin before the Subcommittee on Economic Stabilization of the House Committee on Banking, Finance & Urban Affairs, 1/31/84; and related documents.
  - Industrial Policy [folder 2 of 2], 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Industrial Relations Research Association, N.Y. Chapter, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Industry Negotiations, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    Re holiday payments.
  - Infants', Children's and Girls' Sportswear and Coat Association, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Initiative Committee for National Economic Planning, 1975-1976 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    (Chaikin, Member) Correspondence re activities of Committee.
  - Inquiries, 1981-1986 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    Requests for copies of speeches, information, suggestions, references, etc.
  - Institute for Socioeconomic Studies, 1980-1986 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    Correspondence re article written by Chaikin for the Institute's publication; participation in conferences and related routine.
  - Institute of Collective Bargaining and Group Relations, Inc., 1976 (Box 31, Folder 17a)
  - Instituto Americano Para O Desenvolvimento, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Insurance, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Insurance Workers, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions [folder 1 of 2], 1978-1986 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    Includes circulars, program of 13th World Congress of the ICFTU, form letters to members, constitution and report.
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1986 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - International Labor Program, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - International Labour Organization [folder 1 of 3], 1976-1985 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    Chaikin, a worker/delegate to ILO Conferences, 1976 and 1980; copies of Frank W. McCulloch correspondence re U.S. membership in ILO; and publications.
  - International Labour Organization [folder 2 of 3], 1976-1985 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - International Labour Organization [folder 3 of 3], 1976-1985 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - International Rescue Committee, 1976-1986 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    (Chaikin, Member, Board of Trustees) re support from ILGWU for Cambodian refugees and others; minutes and report.
  - International Sakharov Hearings, 1980 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    re financial.
  - International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers Federation, 1978-1986 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    Re problems in South Africa and Chile; re notices and agendas of Executive Committee meetings; publications.
  - International Union of Operating Engineers, 1980-1986 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    President, J.C. Turner thanking Chaikin for becoming a member of National Planning Association's Board.
  - Interviews, 1980-1983 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    Re interviews with U.S. News and World Report; program, "It's Your Business"; CBS Series "American Labor"; "Today" Show, and others.
  - Invitations, 1974-1985 (Box 32, Folder 1-11)
    Invitations from groups, institutions, and organizations to participate in conferences, discussions, seminars and various programs.
  - Irish Republican Clubs, USA and Canada, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    Re immigrant workers.
  - Israel, 1979-1983 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Israel, Embassy of, 1978-1985 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    Re Israel's apparel shipments to U.S. under the Textile and Apparel Enforcement Act.
  - Israel Labour Party, 1980-1984 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Israel. Golda Meir, 1978-1984 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    Includes packet, "U.S. Presidential Delegation to the Funeral Services for Her Excellency Golda Meir"; re financial support for the Golda Meir Association for Labour Education in Israel.
  - Italian-American Labor Council, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    Re Four Freedoms Award to Chaikin; and contributions for earthquake victims of Southern Italy.
  - Italy, 1978 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    Includes Mrs. Chaikin's notes on trip and related documents.
  - Izod, Ltd. [folder 1 of 2], 1983-1985 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    Re use of contractors in some divisions and extending current agreements and related documents.
  - Izod, Ltd. [folder 2 of 2], 1983-1985 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Izzo, Olindo L., 1982 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - J. Gallery Inc., 1984 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Legal correspondence re firm engaging in the menswear industry.
  - J. John Fox Public Service Foundation, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Jackson, Henry M. Foundation, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    Includes 4 p. White House release, "Remarks of the President at Posthumous Presentation of the Medal of Freedom to Henry Jackson."
  - Jacob K. Javits Convention Center, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    Includes reports of construction schedule, etc.
  - Jaffe, Reuben, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Japan, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    Re Labour Summit and related documents.
  - Japan, 1980-1981 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    Correspondence with Tadanobu Usami, President, Japanese Federation of Textile, Garment, Chemical Workers re U.S.-Japan Foundation, meeting arrangements and miscellaneous.
  - Japan, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    With Moriyuki Motono, Ambassador and Consul General re Japan-U.S. economic relations and related routine.
  - Japan [folder 1 of 3], 1983 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    Includes "Conference Papers of the Sixth Shimoda Conference," September 1983 in which Chaikin was a participant; and related documents.
  - Japan [folder 2 of 3], 1983 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Japan [folder 3 of 3], 1983 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Japan, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    Publications and correspondence re meeting of the U.S./Japan Network and Japanese Labor Leaders and Industrialists in Tokyo, April 1985.
  - Japan [folder 1 of 2], 1985 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    Packet and publications re Tokyo trip.
  - Japan [folder 2 of 2], 1985 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Japan Summit [folder 1 of 4], 1979 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    Includes press releases; statements by Chaikin, articles, minutes, lists of participants, summary of labor summit by Mrs. Chaikin, handwritten notes and other related documents.
  - Japan Summit [folder 2 of 4], 1979 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Japan Summit [folder 3 of 4], 1979 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Japan Summit [folder 4 of 4], 1979 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Jewish Daily Forward, 1974-1984 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    Re financial contributions and articles by and about Chaikin appearing in the Forward.
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1976-1985 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    Documents and correspondence re activities of the Committee.
  - Jewish National Fund, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Johnson Foundation, 1983-1984 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Johnson, Phyllis, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Joint Council for Economic Education, 1981-1982 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Joint Foundation Support, Inc., 1984 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Jonathan Logan, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    Re United Merchants and Manufacturers taking control of Jonathan Logan.
  - Jonker, Frederick, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    Routine
  - Justice, 1984-1986 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    Correspondence re an article in Justice concerning Susquehanna Sportswear and R & J Industries as inaccurate and related routine.
  - Kampelman, Max M., 1986 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Kaplan, Richard M., 1982 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    Personal correspondence.
  - Kennedy, John F., 1959-1979 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    Invitation to the dedication ceremony of the JFK Library; also includes one related routine letter to Chaikin.
  - Kennedy, Robert F. (Memorial), 1984 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    Form letter from Ethel Kennedy re RFK Memorial-Human Rights Award.
  - Kennedy, Ted (Edward M.), 1969-1982 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    Includes copy of speech by Kennedy to the Wisconsin AFL-CIO and other personal notes of thanks for support and encouragement.
  - Kleeblatt, Melvin, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Koch, Edward I. [folder 1 of 2], 1981-1986 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    Re political support and fund raising; 75th Anniversary of Triangle Fire; request for Chaikin to serve on the Task Force on Water Conservation; industrial homework, youth unemployment and related routine.
  - Koch, Edward I. [folder 2 of 2], 1981-1986 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Kott, Israel, 1982 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    Personal.
  - Kratz, D., 1976 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - LaGuardia Memorial House, 1977-1982 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Re activities.
  - Labor and Higher Education, 1982-1986 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Labor Day, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Newspaper clippings.
  - Lacoste-Briones, Michele, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Ladies Apparel Contractors Association, Inc., 1979 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Landsorganisationen I Sverige, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Lantos, Tom, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    ILGWU Campaign Committee re Tom Lantos for Congress fund raising activities.
  - Latin America, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    Includes articles re developments in Latin America.
  - Lawrence, 1977-1985 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Leadership Conference, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - League For Industrial Democracy, 1977-1987 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    (Chaikin, Vice-President) Re activities of the League.
  - League of Women Voters, 1978-1984 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    (Chaikin, Member of Public Advisory Committee for the 1980 Presidential Debates); re financial contributions.
  - Leahy, Patrick, J., 1986 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    (Chaikin, Steering Committee) Re fund raising.
  - Learning Disabilities, 1972-1978 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    Includes Mrs. Chaikin's correspondence.
  - Legal Insurance, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Legislation [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1983 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    Correspondence re Export Trading Companies Act; Tris-treated Sleepwear; employment of veterans; Community Assistance and Revitalization Act; Urban Enterprise Bill; social security; sweatshops and others.
  - Legislation [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1983 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Lehigh Frocks of Pennsylvania, Inc., 1984-1986 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    Re violations of agreement by sending work to non-union contractor.
  - Leslie Fay Company, 1984-1986 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    Re negotiations.
  - Letters To Senators and Representatives Re U.S. Economy, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    Form letters and mailing list.
  - Levin, Carl, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    Re financial support for Senator Levin's campaign.
  - Levine, Arthur, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    Re personnel for Organization Department.
  - Levinson, Jacob, 1978-1979 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Liberal Party, 1980-1985 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Lilly Endowment Inc. (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Lincoln Center for Performing Arts, 1977-1985 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    Re 20th Anniversary celebration, contributions, etc.
  - Lipton, Jack, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Little, Kevin, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Long Island Jewish-Hillside Medical Center [folder 1 of 2], 1978-1983 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    Re testimonial dinner in honor of Chaikin and correspondence re Chaikin's support and interest.
  - Long Island Jewish-Hillside Medical Center [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1983 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Lopatin, Harry (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Louis Calder Foundation, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Maidenform, Inc., 1985 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Mainstream, Inc. [folder 1 of 2], 1975-1985 (Box 34, Folder 34)
    (Chaikin, Member, Board of Directors) Re contributions and activities; also includes minutes and reports.
  - Mainstream, Inc. [folder 2 of 2], 1975-1985 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Management Engineering Department, 1975-1982 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    Correspondence with staff engineers re problems in various shops.
  - Mansfield, Mike, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    Related routine personal.
  - March of Dimes, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Maritime Port Council of Greater NY and Vicinity, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Marlene Industries, 1985-1986 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    Re NLRB case and settlement.
  - Marshall, C. N., 1982 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Martin Luther King, Jr. Center for Nonviolent Social Change, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    Re financial contributions; Chaikin, participant in 6th Annual Institute on Nonviolence.
  - Maryland Home Economics Association, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Master Agreements Firms [folder 1 of 3], 1974-1984 (Box 34, Folder 44)
    Correspondence re many firms regarding negotiations and related documentation (Bobbie Brooks, Puritan Fashions, Genesco Inc., Jonathan Logan, Calvin Klein and others).
  - Master Agreements Firms [folder 2 of 3], 1974-1984 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - Master Agreements Firms [folder 3 of 3], 1974-1984 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - Maurer, Warren, 1979 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Mayor's Office of the Apparel Industry, 1974-1976 (Box 34, Folder 48)
    Re proposal for a Clothing Assistance Administration; clothing stamps.
  - McIntosh Foundation, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 49)
  - Menninger Foundation, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 50)
  - Mental Health Association of Nassau County, 1982-1989 (Box 34, Folder 51)
    Re fund raising.
  - Merchandising Group, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 51a)
    Survey of apparel retail stores re imports.
  - Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Metzer, Morton, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Mexico, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Midtown Realty Owners Association, Inc., 1976 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Milan, Mike, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Miller, Arnold, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Millman, Richard M., 1978 (Box 34, Folder 58)
    Legal correspondence re housing for the elderly.
  - Milstein, Hyman, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - Model Garment Company, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Moliff, Howard, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Moynihan, Daniel P., 1976-1984 (Box 34, Folder 62)
    (Chaikin, Co-Chair Labor for Moynihan Committee) 22 p. paper by Moynihan, "World Trade and the Wealth of a Nation" and comments to Chaikin from ILG staff on the paper; contributions, lists, dinner program and related routine.
  - Murarchik, Emanuel, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Mutual Redevelopment Houses, Inc., 1982-1984 (Box 34, Folder 64)
    Re cooperative housing.
  - Nabash, Pete, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Names and Addresses. Senators and Representatives. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Nantucket Naturals, Inc., 1980 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Nation, The, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    Correspondence with editor re article, "The Great Japan Debate."
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1975-1987 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    Re fund raising; Roy Wilkins 75th Birthday Celebration; invitation for Chaikin to speak at 67th Annual Convention; re meetings of the Board of Trustees of the NAACP Special Contribution Fund of which Chaikin was a member and related routine.
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People. Legal Defense and Educational Fund, 1977- 1986 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    Re contributions; Chaikin participant for Annual Civil Rights Institute and related routine.
  - National Center for Productivity and Quality of Working Life, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - National Child Labor Committee, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - National Commission on Resources for Youth, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - National Conference on Human Rights, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    Correspondence from Bayard Rustin thanking Chaikin for his participation in the conference.
  - National Consumers League, 1982-1986 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    (Chaikin, Member, Special Labor Committee) Re contributions and appeals for financial support.
  - National Council of Senior Citizens, 1979-1985 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    Re working with the trade union movement toward mutual goals; financial support and imports.
  - National Jewish Hospital-National Asthma Center, 1979-1984 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    Re fund raising efforts.
  - National Jewish Monthly, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - National Planning Association, 1975-1982 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    (Chaikin, Board Member, and Member of the Committee on the Coordination of U.S. Foreign Economic Policy) Includes minutes of the Board and related routine.
  - National Policy Exchange, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    New release; 8 p. paper entitled "The National Policy
  - National Resource Center, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - National Retirement Fund (ILGWU), 1980-1986 (Box 35, Folder 18-30)
    Many inquiries from employees and former employees regarding pension benefits; reports; financial reports; minutes and other related correspondence.
  - National Strategy Information Center, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    Includes minutes of first meeting of the Advisory Committee and related routine.
  - National Union of Hosiery and Knitwear Workers, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    Re foreign union visitor.
  - National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers, 1979-1981 (Box 35, Folder 33)
    Includes address by Chairman I.G. Brace and related routine.
  - National Urban Coalition, 1976-1981 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    Correspondence re contributions and activities of the Coalition.
  - National Urban League, 1976-1985 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    (Chaikin, Member, Board of Directors) Re contributions; minutes, 9/15/81.
  - Negotiations [folder 1 of 5], 1973-1982 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    Re imports billing provision, health insurance, lists of demands, reports, transcript of negotiating session between Dressmakers Joint Council and Employers' Associations (1982); charts, handwritten notes, proposed agreements, Reports of Task Force on Strike Preparations, 11/16/78; and miscellaneous.
  - Negotiations [folder 2 of 5], 1973-1982 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Negotiations [folder 3 of 5], 1973-1982 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Negotiations [folder 4 of 5], 1973-1982 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Negotiations [folder 5 of 5], 1973-1982 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - New Directions, Inc., 1978-1981 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - New England Apparel Manufacturers Association, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    Re organizing efforts and many other issues.
  - New England Macintosh, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    Re financial problems of a small manufacturer in the coat industry.
  - New Leader, 1977-1985 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    Re financial support; personal and related routine editorial correspondence.
  - New Members' Classes (Box 36, Folder 10)
    Undated. 10 p. leaflet, "New Members' Class" re explanation of union benefits and services.
  - New Republic, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - New York Citizens for Balanced Transportation, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    (Chaikin, Member) Correspondence re Westside Highway Project (Westway).
  - New York, City of, 1975-1985 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    Re financial problems of N.Y.C. Board of Education; re location of proposed new convention center; political support; bid for 1984 summer Olympics; clothing assistance program; potential sites for ILGWU building; city planning workshop/conference; dredging of New York Harbor; effects on Chinatown with new zoning policy; water conservation; security for garment center; problems of city's apparel industry; 4 p. "Testimony for the Commission on the Year 2000" by Chaikin, 5/9/85 before City of New York, Commission on the Year 2000; N.Y. Building Records Collection in Municipal Archives and other related routine.
  - New York City Central Labor Council, 1974-1985 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    Re fund raising for establishment of a Yiddish National Theatre; Annual Award Dinner of Black Trade Unionists Leadership Committee honoring Chaikin; Labor Day Parade; and related routine.
  - New York City Public Development Corporation, 1978-1984 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    (Chaikin, Member, Board of Directors) Re meetings and activities.
  - New York Consumer Assembly, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    Re awards dinner honoring Chaikin (Consumer Merit Award).
  - New York Convention Center [folder 1 of 2], 1982-1988 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    (Chaikin, Chairman of the Board) Re construction delays, costs, status reports, Board Minutes, public vs. private management of the Center and related routine.
  - New York Convention Center [folder 2 of 2], 1982-1988 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - New York District Export Council, 1981-1983 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    (Chaikin, Member) Re export expansion activities.
  - New York Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    (Chaikin, Member, Board of Trustees) Includes minutes, guidelines for grant application, correspondence and related routine.
  - New York Life Foundation (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - New York Loft Board, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - New York and New Jersey, Port Authority of, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    Re study of trucking problems.
  - New York Regional Economists Society, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - New York Society, 1982-1984 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    (Chaikin, President) Related routine.
  - New York State, 1977-1988 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    To Lillian Roberts (Commissioner of Labor) and others re sweatshops and homework; from Gov. Hugh Carey inviting Chaikin to attend "Topridge Seminar on the Future of the State"; from Carey re State's economy; N.Y. International Fashion Fair; dinner by NYS Democrats honoring Chaikin; industrial homework; program for 1st Anniversary Celebration of Gov. Cuomo; information re NYS Martin Luther King Jr. Commission; and other miscellaneous.
  - New York State Council of Senior Citizens, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - New York State Division of Alcoholism and Alcohol Abuse, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    Re funding for programs.
  - New York State Festival, 1981-1985 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    (Chaikin, Co-chairman) Minutes and correspondence re meetings, arrangements and miscellaneous.
  - New York Times, 1982-1986 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    Editorial correspondence.
  - New York University, 1978-1986 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    re programs and conferences.
  - New York Urban Coalition, 1974-1986 (Box 36, Folder 32)
    (Chaikin, Board of Directors) Correspondence re salary levels of officers and employees; fund raising and activities.
  - New York Urban Development, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 33)
    Correspondence re problems in garment center; 42nd Street Development Project; 75 p. paper, "The Impact of the 42nd Street Redevelopment Project on the Garment Industry" by Roger Waldinger for the Federation of Apparel Manufacturers.
  - New York Urban League, 1976-1986 (Box 36, Folder 34)
    (Chaikin, Member, Board of Directors) Includes by-laws; correspondence re issues and activities.
  - Nickles, Don, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 35)
    Re industrial homework.
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1972 (Box 36, Folder 36)
    Form letters re Vietnam War.
  - No Greater Love, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 37)
    Form letter from Carol Burnett and Roger Staubach re campaign to free the hostages in Iran.
  - North Bellmore Public Library, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Northeast Apparel Association, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Northern Textile Association, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Northside Center, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Notre Dame Conference on Economics, 1983-1986 (Box 36, Folder 42)
    Re Chaikin's participation in a symposium on Catholic Social Teaching and the American Economy.
  - Occupational Alcoholism Project, 1984-1985 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Letters re funding for project and termination of state funding.
  - Office and Professional Employees Union, Local 153, 1979-1983 (Box 37, Folder 1a)
  - Office of the President, 1981-1986 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    Re dues increase; and related routine matters.
  - Ofir, Michele, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    Re establishment of a Chair at Tel Aviv University, Labor Studies Department by American Friends of Tel Aviv in the name of David Dubinsky.
  - Olin Foundation. (Box 37, Folder 4)